Finding Aid for Camp Al-Gon-Quian (Burt Lake, Mich.) records, 1925-1967
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Campers files 1925-1967
  - Chronological 1925-1967
    - 1952
      [Restricted until January 1 2052 ]
      - Amalfitano, Neil (Box 14)
      - Buchart, Jim (Box 14)
      - Cahow, John (Box 14)
      - Collins, Peter (includes George) (Box 14)
      - Davies, Jim (Box 14)
      - Drackett, Danny (Box 14)
      - Folger, Bill (Box 14)
      - Goodrich, Jimmy (includes Bobby) (Box 14)
      - Hall, Geoffrey (Box 15)
      - Henry, Brian (Box 15)
      - Holmes, Gordon Oesterling (Box 15)
      - Hubly, Bill (Box 15)
      - Jennings, Harry (Box 15)
      - Kaatz, Dick (Box 15)
      - Kleinschmit, Arthur (Box 15)
      - Kollen, Mike (includes Pete) (1952-1953) (Box 15)
      - Kroeber, Dick (Box 15)
      - DeHaan, Jon (Box 15)
      - Lentini, Dick (Box 15)
      - May, Stuart (Box 15)
      - Nagel, Eddie (Box 15)
      - Nebel, Charles (Box 15)
      - Newman, Mel (Box 15)
      - Norman, Allen E. (Box 15)
      - Perkins, Jim (Box 15)
      - Pettit, Bill (Box 15)
      - Petty, Lenny (Box 15)
      - Price, Hickman (High) (includes Marston) (Box 15)
      - Obert, Don (Box 15)
      - Richards, Edward (Box 15)
      - Riebenack, Pete (Box 15)
      - Riecker, Teddy (Box 15)
      - Roberts, Doug (Box 15)
      - Salisbury, Dick (Box 15)
      - Scherer, Walt (Box 15)
      - Sharrock, Jack (includes Dave) (Box 15)
      - Slocombe, Walter (Box 15)
      - Stahl, John T. (Box 15)
      - Stepan, Paul (includes John) (Box 15)
      - Thomas, Jim (Box 15)
      - Tompkins, Bob (Box 15)
      - Vogt, Clifford (Sandy) (includes Pete) (Box 15)
      - Wade, Allen (includes Mark) (Box 15)
      - Wetherby, Steve (Box 15)
      - Whiting, Jock (Box 15)
      - Wood, Neil (includes Winston "Winnie") (1948-1954) (Box 15)
      - Wright, Jimmy (includes Teddy) (Box 15)
    - 1953
      [Restricted until January 1 2053 ]
      - Anderson, Buzz (Box 15)
      - Arnold, Bob (includes John) (1953-1954) (Box 15)
      - Bartlowe, Sterling (Box 15)
      - Bedford, Mike (Box 15)
      - Bigelow, Timothy Lawson (Tim) 1949 (Box 15)
      - Bouchey, Jimmie (Box 15)
      - Brandt, Ricky (Box 15)
      - Cook, Dave (Box 15)
      - Curtis, Boots (Box 15)
      - Davis, Steve (includes Harve) (Box 15)
      - Fischer, Rich (includes Dave) (1953-1955) (Box 15)
      - Fowler, Jack (includes James Harold "Jimmy") (1953-1957) (Box 15)
      - Gentry, Howard (includes Tommy) (1953-1954) (Box 15)
      - Grady, Michael (includes Steve) (1953-1955) (Box 15)
      - Greiner, Tony (Box 15)
      - Herrick, Todd (Box 15)
      - Hoobler, Raymond (Box 15)
      - Howell, Bob (Box 15)
      - Johnson, Tom (Box 15)
      - Kelly, Donny (Box 15)
      - King, George (Box 15)
      - Leach, Bob (Box 15)
      - Lewis, Dave (Box 15)
      - Mahar, Jim (Box 15)
      - Mayne, Joe (Box 15)
      - McGuire, Johnny (includes Michael) (Box 15)
      - McMillin, Jamie (Box 15)
      - Montague, Bob (Box 15)
      - Murphy, Mark (Box 15)
      - Norman, Anthony (Box 15)
      - O'Connor, Johnny (Box 15)
      - O'Shaughnessy, Tim (Box 15)
      - Parke, Charlie & Clement (Box 16)
      - Pfeiffer, Craig (Box 16)
      - Poirier, Alex (Box 16)
      - Post, Mike (includes Jerry) (1953-1955) (Box 16)
      - Rezanka, John Charles (Box 16)
      - Risdon, Dick (includes Tom) (1951-1953) (Box 16)
      - Rudell, Bill (Box 16)
      - Sacks, Frankie (Box 16)
      - Sager, Dudley (includes Dave & Doug) (1951-1953) (Box 16)
      - Schmidt, Gary (Box 16)
      - Schreur, Dave (includes Ammon Jeffrey "Jeff") (1953-1957) (Box 16)
      - Seyffert, Eddie (1951) (Box 16)
      - Smith, James Allen (Box 16)
      - Smith, Preston Walker (1949) (Box 16)
      - Stanford, Skip (Box 16)
      - Stewart, Davey (includes Bobby) (Box 16)
      - Quinn, Lawrence R. (Box 16)
      - Tiernan, Tom (Box 16)
      - VanderVeen, Jimmy (Box 16)
      - Weymouth, Butch (Box 16)
    - 1954
      [Restricted until January 1 2054 ]
      - Adams, Morrie (Box 16)
      - Alfenito, John (Box 16)
      - Andreae, Frank (Box 16)
      - Avery, Toby (Box 16)
      - Branion, Bobby (Box 16)
      - Cain, Steve (Box 16)
      - Carpenter, Johnny (Box 16)
      - Cooper, Jim (Box 16)
      - Cramton, Gary (Box 16)
      - Crutchfield, Woody (Box 16)
      - Curtis, Mack (Box 16)
      - Detwiler, Johnny (Box 16)
      - Elliott, Davie (Box 16)
      - Emmett, John P. (Box 16)
      - Furstenberg, Bill (Box 16)
      - Garza, Bobby (Box 16)
      - Griffin, Joe (Box 16)
      - Grimm, Bob (includes Dick) (1954-1955) (Box 16)
      - Harrison, Mac (Box 16)
      - Imbrie, Will (Box 16)
      - Keller, Joe (Box 16)
      - Lenz, Ricky (Box 16)
      - Levine, Tommy (Box 16)
      - Levy, Joe (Box 16)
      - Link, Roy (Box 16)
      - McKay, Rusty (Box 16)
      - O'Neill, Bob (Box 16)
      - Polster, David (Box 16)
      - Rahilly, Larry (Box 16)
      - Ratterman, Tommy (includes Bambi, Mike) (Box 16)
      - Roe, Johnny (Box 16)
      - Self, Bill (1955) (Box 16)
      - Simmons, Dave (Box 16)
      - Smiggen, Bob (Box 16)
      - Stearns, Clark (Box 16)
      - Stebbins, Dickie (Box 16)
      - Stoll, Brian (Box 16)
      - Stolorow, Mark (Box 16)
      - Todd, Chuck (includes Jim) (Box 16)
      - VanHouten, Buzzy (includes Pete) (Box 16)
      - Walker, Bob (Box 16)
      - Walker, Wink (Box 16)
      - Wardwell, Johnny (Box 16)
      - White, Alec (Box 16)
      - Whitehead, Jeff (Box 16)
      - Wilson, Jim (Box 16)
      - Wilson, Stan (includes Bob) (Box 16)
      - Winchester, Frank (Box 16)
    - 1955
      [Restricted until January 1 2055 ]
      - Adcock, Johnny (Box 16)
      - Addison, Robbie (Box 16)
      - Allen, Jim (Box 16)
      - Badger, Graeme (Box 16)
      - Baldwin, Teddy (Box 16)
      - Bergstrom, Van (Box 16)
      - Bertling, Bill (Box 16)
      - Bogen, David (Box 16)
      - Borusch, Bob (Box 16)
      - Bosch, Chuckie (Box 16)
      - Bradley, Tommy (includes Bruce) (1955-1956) (Box 16)
      - Bremer, Joey (Box 16)
      - Broeman, Rol (includes Billy) (Box 16)
      - Burcaw, Kenny (includes Bobby) (Box 16)
      - Cassell, Jim (includes Bill) (Box 16)
      - Cheley, Don (Box 16)
      - Clark, Bill (Box 16)
      - Clayton, Tommy (Box 17)
      - Clements, Mike (Box 17)
      - Colker, Dick (Box 17)
      - Cook, Stan (Box 17)
      - Daniels, Dick (Box 17)
      - Dillman, Dave (Box 17)
      - Dittman, Robbie (Box 17)
      - Downes, Mike (Box 17)
      - Earl, Dick (Box 17)
      - Eberts, Jerry (includes Billy) (Box 17)
      - Ellstrom, Ole (Box 17)
      - Estes, Curt (Box 17)
      - Foster, Jim (Box 17)
      - Gregory, Doug (includes Rich) (Box 17)
      - Griswold, Joe (Box 17)
      - Gurdjian, Ron (includes Ricky) (1954-1955) (Box 17)
      - Gusfa, Connie (Box 17)
      - Heames, Bob (Box 17)
      - Helfrick, Charles (Box 17)
      - Hummer, Joe (Box 17)
      - Irons, Bruce (Box 17)
      - Irwin, John (includes Win) (Box 17)
      - Keegan, Bob (Box 17)
      - Kelson, John (includes Dave) (Box 17)
      - Kraus, Gene (Box 17)
      - LaPointe, Frank J. (Box 17)
      - Leach, Bob (Box 17)
      - Leighton, John (Box 17)
      - Lindell, Doug (includes Charley) (Box 17)
      - MacHarg, Davy (Box 17)
      - MacIntyre, Dennis (Box 17)
      - MacKay, Jack (Box 17)
      - McClure, Clyde (Box 17)
      - McCune, Chuck (Box 17)
      - Miles, Mike (Box 17)
      - Miller, Jeff (Box 17)
      - Moloney, Paul (Box 17)
      - Nelles, Wally (Box 17)
      - Parke, Chuck (includes Clem) (Box 17)
      - Plowman, Tommy (Box 17)
      - Price, Jim (Box 17)
      - Rassas, George (includes Kevin & Nicholas "Doc") (Box 17)
      - Reed, Mike (includes Dave) (Box 17)
      - Rice, Johnny (includes Tom) (Box 17)
      - Richardson, Don (Box 17)
      - Risdon, Russ (Box 17)
      - Rosenfeld, Davey (includes Mark) (Box 17)
      - Sangster, Bobby (Box 17)
      - Schmidt, Bill (Box 17)
      - Shafer, Butch (Box 17)
      - Slessman, D. B. (Box 17)
      - Stanford, Lou (Box 17)
      - Steed, Bucky (Box 17)
      - Steffans, Eddie (Box 17)
      - Stites, Johnny (Box 17)
      - Tan, Eng (Box 17)
      - Tennant, Derk (Box 17)
      - Wear, Duke (Box 17)
      - Welch, Jimmy (includes Craig Jr.) (1954-1955) (Box 17)
      - Wiggins, William James, III (Bill) (Box 17)
      - Wilcox, Frankie (Box 17)
      - Williams, Rick (Box 17)
      - Woodworth, Fred L. (1957) (Box 17)
      - Wright, Sherm (Box 17)
    - 1956
      [Restricted until January 1 2056 ]
      - Andrews, Pete (Box 18)
      - Bailey, David (Box 18)
      - Baker, Lee (Box 18)
      - Beard, Louis (Box 18)
      - Butcher, Kenny (Box 18)
      - Carter, Johnny (Box 18)
      - Cassidy, Kevin (Box 18)
      - Clark, Joe (Box 18)
      - Crouse, Timmy (includes Peter) (1956-1962) (Box 18)
      - Curtiss, Carl (Curt) (Box 18)
      - Dalton, Norman Perry (Box 18)
      - Dascola, David (includes Robert Michael "Bobby") (1956-1958) (Box 18)
      - Fletcher, Steve (Box 18)
      - Forkner, Jim (Box 18)
      - Fortino, Steve (Box 18)
      - Gordon, Brit (includes Tracy & Scotty) (Box 18)
      - Greene, Geoff (Box 18)
      - Heritier, Dave (Box 18)
      - Hinderer, Jim (Box 18)
      - Holland, Jeep (includes Jomp) (1956-1957) (Box 18)
      - Jones, Jay (Box 18)
      - Lapham, Bruce (Box 18)
      - Lasch, Larry (Box 18)
      - Lee, Billy (Box 18)
      - Lincoln, Rusty (Box 18)
      - Lyon, Chuck (Box 18)
      - Mahaffey, Mark (Box 18)
      - Mahon, John (Box 18)
      - McKay, Tad (includes George Wm. Jr.) (1956-1957) (Box 18)
      - Moore, Lee (includes Frank & George) (1956-1958) (Box 18)
      - Ogley, Bill (Box 18)
      - Oliver, John (Box 18)
      - Penrose, Clem (Box 18)
      - Pletscher, Hank (Box 18)
      - Searles, Barry (Box 18)
      - Seyffert, Gordon (Box 18)
      - Sisson, Lance (Box 18)
      - Skae, Ned (Box 18)
      - Sullivan, Mark (Box 18)
      - Tally, Truman (Box 18)
      - Thompson, Dave (Box 18)
      - Thompson, Pete (Box 18)
      - Watkins, Hamilton (Box 18)
      - Welch, Gale (Box 18)
      - Willie, Roice (includes Brent Stanley & Stan Curtis) (1956-1963) (Box 18)
    - 1957
      [Restricted until January 1 2057 ]
      - Benner, Al (Box 18)
      - Blackburn, Jeffery H. (Jeff) (Box 18)
      - Blackstone, George (Box 18)
      - Boyer, Tom (includes Frank "Hank") (1957-1958) (Box 18)
      - Breer, Bert (includes Carl) (Box 18)
      - Brown, Clinton (Box 18)
      - Bruggeman, Tonton "Tony" (includes Pappy, Henry, Jack Anthony, Joseph, Patrick J.) (1957-1961) (Box 18)
      - Burks, Ned (Box 18)
      - Campbell, Darrell (Skip) (Box 18)
      - Campbell, Don Alan (Box 18)
      - Cauchois, Gage (Box 18)
      - Coe, Sandy (Box 18)
      - Cord, Cameron Wayne (Corky) (Box 18)
      - Cunningham, Charles Frederick "Fred" (Box 18)
      - Early, Steve (Box 18)
      - Evans, Robert Jr. (Box 18)
      - Fahrner, Jackie (Box 18)
      - Flintermann, Andy (Box 18)
      - Glanz, Rick (Box 18)
      - Gould, Bruce F. (Box 18)
      - Hall, Thomas James Jr. "Tommy" (Box 18)
      - Healy, Charles Edw. (Box 18)
      - Holt, Jack (Box 18)
      - Hopewell, Stanley John (Stan) (Box 18)
      - Horste, David (Box 18)
      - Johnson, Paul E. "Pej" (Box 18)
      - Jones, Jeff (Box 18)
      - Kelly, Lark (Box 18)
      - Keyser, William Earl "Bill" (includes Bruce Hartley "Boop") (Box 18)
      - Lamb, Robert Jeffrey (Jeff) (Box 19)
      - Lathers, John Robert (Johnny) (Box 19)
      - Leland, Joshua (Josh) (Box 19)
      - Leonelli, Lance (Box 19)
      - Lohr, Bill (Box 19)
      - Loop, Chris (Box 19)
      - Mackey, Walter Jay (Rusty) (Box 19)
      - Malcolm, John Putnam (Johnny) (Box 19)
      - McCullough, Bill (Box 19)
      - McKee, Philip Leopold (Phil) (Box 19)
      - Olson, Lance (includes Nels & Christopher Scott "Chris") (1957-1961) (Box 19)
      - Ostermann, Hal (Box 19)
      - Peckinpaugh, Peck (Box 19)
      - Rabinovitch, Mark (Box 19)
      - Rickard, Robert Raleigh "Robbie" (Box 19)
      - Rider, Pete (Box 19)
      - Robinson, Burnett (Box 19)
      - Ross, Bob (Box 19)
      - Shaeffer, Leland Dale (Box 19)
      - Sheasby, John Jimmy (includes John Frederick) (Box 19)
      - Spitzley, Jim (Box 19)
      - Teeple, Ross Jr. "Junior" (Box 19)
      - Weber, Mark (Box 19)
      - Weintraub, Gary D. (Box 19)
      - White, Dave (Box 19)
      - Yax, Gerry (Box 19)
    - 1958
      [Restricted until January 1 2058 ]
      - Achterhoff, Bobby (Box 19)
      - Barbour, Thomas Chittenden "Tommy" (Box 19)
      - Barrows, Frank Clifford (includes Peter B.) (1958-1961) (Box 19)
      - Bentlage, Roger Eric "Rog" (Box 19)
      - Bernstein, Robert Boyd "Bob" (Box 19)
      - Bradshaw, James Lloyd "Jimmy" (Box 19)
      - Brown, Henry Pell Jr. "Pell" (includes Kent Masterson "Kenny") (1958-1959) (Box 19)
      - Brett, Bradford Arnold "Skip" (Box 19)
      - Bunday, John Frederick (Box 19)
      - Bursley, Philip Everette (Box 19)
      - Caveny, Christopher "Chris" (Box 19)
      - Davison, Fent (Box 19)
      - Faye, Leslie Eitig "Lee" (Box 19)
      - Foote, Robert L. "Robbie" (Box 19)
      - Ford, Frederick Brier "Ricky" (includes Robert Ernest "Robby" (Box 19)
      - Franklin, James Lincoln "Jim" (Box 19)
      - Geier, Frederick Wurlitzer "Fritz" (Box 19)
      - Hall, Carter Wilkinson "Terry" (Box 19)
      - Heavenrich, Max Philip (Box 19)
      - Hendee, Richmond Shreve "Ric" (includes Steven Hunter "Stebo") (Box 19)
      - Holley, David Cullen (Box 19)
      - Holley, George M. III (Box 19)
      - Hord, Thomas Doggett "Tom" (Box 19)
      - Husted, Clark Edgell (Box 19)
      - King, Robert Lee "Bob" (Box 19)
      - Klopfenstein, Charles Edward "Chuck" (Box 19)
      - Knoop, Rudolph Wurlitzer "Roddy" (Box 19)
      - Kowalk, Lawrence Carl "Larry" (Box 19)
      - Lathrop, Henry Krike (Box 19)
      - Lee, Roger William "Roge" (Box 19)
      - Marks, Standish Backus "Sandy" (Box 19)
      - Matthews, Calvin Carl "Cal" (Box 19)
      - Maxon, Philip Nelson "Phil" (Box 19)
      - May, Thomas P. "Tom" (Box 19)
      - McCammon, William Gavin "Bill" (Box 19)
      - Moen, James C. "Jimmie" (Box 19)
      - Morris, Richard Risdon "Rick" (Box 19)
      - Myers, Craig Alan (Box 19)
      - Pittman, Steuart (includes John) (1955-1958) (Box 19)
      - Raisbeck, John Wallace "Johnny" (Box 19)
      - Read, Michael B. "Mokey" (includes Timothy Byrne "Timmy" (1958-1960) (Box 19)
      - Schaefer, Edward Norman "Ted" (includes Henry Frederick "Fritz") (Box 19)
      - Schiff, Charles Louis "Chuck" (Box 19)
      - Smith, Peter Walldorff "Rusty" (Box 19)
      - Spalding, Lyman A. (Box 19)
      - Stahl, James Philip (Box 19)
      - Steiert, Stephen Edward "Steve" (Box 19)
      - Storrs, Albert Miller "Burr" (Box 19)
      - Surdam, Peter Buhl "Pete" (Box 19)
      - Teysen, Kenneth Duane "Kenny" (includes Gregory John) (1958-1964) (Box 19)
      - Weiss, Paul Edward (includes Mark Charles) (1958-1959) (Box 19)
      - Williams, Henry P. "Phil" (Box 19)
      - Woodruff, Michael L. (Mike) (Box 19)
      - Wottrich, Rick (Box 19)
      - Wrigley, George Alexander (Box 19)
    - 1959
      [Restricted until January 1 2059 ]
      - Allan, Harper Keys "Keys" (Box 20)
      - Baldwin, Craig B. (Box 20)
      - Casterline, Ray J. "Butch" (Box 20)
      - Coale, John B. (includes George) (Box 20)
      - Davis, Charles William "Bill" (includes Michael L.) (Box 20)
      - Freedman, Joe Selin (Box 20)
      - Fuger, Tony (Box 20)
      - Green, Daniel Alien "Danny" (Box 20)
      - Halligan, Robert Fletcher "Bobby" (includes Thomas Michael "Tom") (1959-1965) (Box 20)
      - Keenan, Frederick B. "Fred" or "Fritz" (Box 20)
      - Keller, Howard Joseph "Howdy" (Box 20)
      - Kirsch, Christopher John (Box 20)
      - Loftis, Charles B. Jr. "Chuck" (Box 20)
      - Mac Cutcheon, Samuel (Box 20)
      - McCarthy, Tom (Box 20)
      - McCray, Christopher B. "Kit or "Chris" (Box 20)
      - McKay, George (includes Tad) (Box 20)
      - Morrow, David Vincent "Davy" (Box 20)
      - Morsey, Chase III "Chip" (Box 20)
      - Peet, George Millis (Box 20)
      - Reade, W. Kent (Box 20)
      - Risdon, Joseph Edward "Joe" (Box 20)
      - Roach, Philip "Phil" (Box 20)
      - Runciman, Dave (Box 20)
      - Schorger, John Rodger "Jock" (Box 20)
      - Smith, Randall Clayton "Randy" (Box 20)
      - Stadelman, Kris R. (Box 20)
      - Taylor, Hall (Box 20)
      - Turner, George Loomis "Geo" (Box 20)
      - Van Gelder, Cornelius "Neil" (Box 20)
      - Vry, John Lawrence (Box 20)
      - Weislow, Thomas G. "Tommy" (Box 20)
      - West, William J. Jr. (includes Douglas H.) (Box 20)
      - Willimott, John Thomas (Box 20)
      - Young, William T., Jr. "Bill" (Box 20)
    - 1960
      [Restricted until January 1 2060 ]
      - Arnspiger, Richard Jr. "Dicky" (Box 20)
      - Beatty, Robert D., III "Robbie" (Box 20)
      - Bohmer, Charles Christopher "Chris" (Box 20)
      - Bracken, William McKnight "Will" (Box 20)
      - Carman, Steven "Steve" (Box 20)
      - Cassidy, William A. "Bill" (Box 20)
      - Chickering, William Elbridge, III "Bill" (Box 20)
      - Combs, James Arnold "Jimmy" (Box 20)
      - Copi, Thomas Russell "Tom" (Box 20)
      - Coyle, Stephen J. "Steve" (Box 20)
      - Daugherty, James E. "Jim" (Box 20)
      - Davison, Edward Benson "Ed" (Box 20)
      - Dondanville, Michael Pierre (Box 20)
      - Duboff, David Louis "Dave" (Box 20)
      - Ford, John Battice, IV "Johnny" (Box 20)
      - Gilson, Kenneth Arden "Kenny" (Box 20)
      - Girkins, Kent Harrison (Staff) (Box 20)
      - Glancy, Terrance Alfred "Terry" (Includes Michael McCoy & Peter S.) (Box 20)
      - Heaphy, Robert Thomas "Bobby" (Box 20)
      - Hill, Michael Daley (Box 20)
      - Kaatz, William "Bill" (Box 20)
      - Klein, Charles E. "Chad" or "Chuck" (includes Mark L.) (Box 20)
      - Kollar, John Anton (includes James Anthony & Robert Jeff) (1960-1964) (Box 20)
      - Lennox, John Franklin "Johnny" (Box 20)
      - Nusbaum, Howard Phelps "Howey" (Box 20)
      - Potter, Rex Beresford "Berry" (Box 20)
      - Power, Thomas Goodrich "Tom" (Box 20)
      - Scharbat, Joseph Russell "Joe" (Box 20)
      - Schlechte, John Vincent (Box 20)
      - Schorling, William Harrison "Bill" (Box 20)
      - Sibley, Frederick Merrill, III "Freddie" (Box 20)
      - Smoke, Robert Donald "Bob" (includes Paul John) (1960-1961) (Box 20)
      - Stone, Keith S. (Box 20)
      - Stopher, Robert "Bob" (Box 20)
      - Takesh, Farokh J. (Box 20)
      - Temple, William Abbott "Bill" (Box 20)
      - Wiggins, Christopher "Chris" (Box 20)
      - Williams, Ross Wood "Rossie" (Box 20)
      - Zayti, James Jay "Jim" (Box 20)
    - 1961
      [Restricted until January 1 2061 ]
      - Aikens, Allen (Box 21)
      - Bracken, Alexander Elliott "Sandy" (Box 21)
      - Brescia, Donald (includes Robert John) (1961-1963) (Box 21)
      - Chabut, David George "Dave" (Box 21)
      - Coleman, Thomas "Kelley" (Box 21)
      - Cordell, Thomas Frank "Tom" (Box 21)
      - Edwards, Thomas James "Tom" (Box 21)
      - Fairweather, Peter (Box 21)
      - Foster, Douglas R. "Doug" (Box 21)
      - Gabele, Robert (Box 21)
      - George, Thomas M. "Tom" (Box 21)
      - Hallbertg, Lawrence Curtis (Box 21)
      - Ingersoll, Jon (includes Robert) (1961-1962) (Box 21)
      - Inwood, Jeffrey Jerome "Jeff" (Box 21)
      - Johnson, Jerome Ford "Jory" (Box 21)
      - Johnston, C. Gilman "Johnny" (Box 21)
      - Kaye, Thomas (Box 21)
      - Koch, John Joseph (includes Freddie) (1953-1961) (Box 21)
      - May, Thomas "Tom" (Box 21)
      - Messler, Joseph D. "Dyke" (Box 21)
      - Murphy, James (Box 21)
      - Parke, Charles Christopher "Charlie" (Box 21)
      - Pemberton, John Linley "Jody" (Box 21)
      - Planteroth, John Raymond (Box 21)
      - Porter, Allen Ramsey (includes Donald W. "Don") (1961-1962) (Box 21)
      - Post, Timothy "Tim" (Box 21)
      - Reynolds, Thomas A. "Tom" (Box 21)
      - Rhodes, Charles Dover "Charlie" (Box 21)
      - Ries, Granner Strong "Gran" (Box 21)
      - Ringley, Michael John "Mike" (includes Earl Robert "Robby") (Box 21)
      - Ruckelshaus, Thomas F. "Tommy" (Box 21)
      - Saddler, Robert Laurence "Bob" (Box 21)
      - Schultz, Richard (Box 21)
      - Schuster, Donald Edward "Don" (Box 21)
      - Stranahan, Duane (Box 21)
      - Test, Donald N. "Don" (includes Henry Bryant, William Perryman) (1961-1962) (Box 21)
      - Veras, George "Georgie" (Box 21)
      - Wells, Peter Carleton "Pete" (Box 21)
      - Wolf, Mark Marmon (includes Edward Joseph III, Frank Hoke, Fred Hoke) (1961-1964) (Box 21)
      - Young, William Joseph III "Billy" (Box 21)
    - 1962
      [Restricted until January 1 2062 ]
      - Atkins, Thomas Pearce (Box 21)
      - Bartlett, Robert William "Bart" or "Bob" (Box 21)
      - Battin, Richard Lemoine "Dick" (Box 21)
      - Bauer, John Thos. "Johnny" (Box 21)
      - Boyd, Benjamin Fay "Benny" (Box 21)
      - Bursley, Philip E. (Box 21)
      - Coffman, Harold Stephen "Hal" (Box 21)
      - Daniels, Jon F. (Box 21)
      - DeLong, Daniel Roger "Roger" (Box 21)
      - Denise, David James "Dave" (Box 21)
      - Devereaux, Gordon William (Box 21)
      - Donnelly, William J. "Bill" (includes R. George) (1962-1964) (Box 21)
      - DuPerow, Donald Eugene "Don" (Box 21)
      - Durastanti, Dominic (includes Frank) (Box 21)
      - Eder, Jay (Box 21)
      - Failey, John Noel (Box 21)
      - Fogg, Daniel Thos. "Danny" (Box 21)
      - Garmahusen, John Maxwell (Box 21)
      - Gillespie, Lawrence Wm. "Larry" (Box 21)
      - Glossop, Michael Morgan "Mike" (Box 21)
      - Gordon, James Adams (Box 21)
      - Hall, Ben "Benjie" (Box 21)
      - Harper, Stephen Elliot (Box 21)
      - Hellman, Peter Stuart (includes John Alburn "Jack") (Box 21)
      - Hewitt, Jeffrey Lynn (Box 21)
      - Hills, James Crawford "Buff" (includes David & Peter) (1962-1966) (Box 21)
      - Hull, Roger Wolcott "Rog" (Box 21)
      - Ingersoll, Robert Mason "Bob" (Box 21)
      - Kaufmann, Jeffrey Louis "Jeff" (Box 21)
      - Keithley, Joseph Pearce (includes Roy Faber) (1962-1966) (Box 21)
      - Kern, Otto (Box 21)
      - Leinbach, Eric Thomas (Box 21)
      - Magee, Robert "Bobby" (includes Benjamin Rush "Rusty", Kenneth Wendell "Ken", James Lyndon "Jim") (1962-1966) (Box 21)
      - Myers, Philip Everett "Flip" (Box 21)
      - Nardizzi, Mario Len (Box 21)
      - Neville, Thomas Brown "Tom" (Box 21)
      - Offield, James Sanford "Jim" (Box 21)
      - Ostermann, G. Curtis (Box 21)
      - Redeker, John Elliott (Box 21)
      - Reuter, James M. (Box 21)
      - Robinson, Frederick James (Box 21)
      - Robinson, Jefferson D. "Jeff" (Box 21)
      - Robinson, Michael Thomas (Box 21)
      - Rockwell, Francis William "Bill" (includes Thomas Reardon "Tommy" (Box 22)
      - Savage, Frank Albert (Box 22)
      - Snyder, Thomas Earl "Tom" (Box 22)
      - Tenney, Earl Wallace "Buzzy" (Box 22)
      - Tuttle, Leigh Dexter "Dek" (Box 22)
      - Viger, Peter Edward (Box 22)
      - Watson, Gregory James "Greg" (Box 22)
    - 1963
      [Restricted until January 1 2063 ]
      - Albert, Tommy Russell "Buckshot" (Box 22)
      - Altmansberger, David Christian "Chris" (Box 22)
      - Andreae, Stephen Holden "Steve" (Box 22)
      - Atterbury, Harry Leigman (Box 22)
      - Bayer, Thomas Walter "Tom" (Box 22)
      - Blain, Bruce Scott Murray (Box 22)
      - Boeschenstein, William W. Jr. "Bill" (Box 22)
      - Buhrman, Jeffrey Peter "Jeff" (Box 22)
      - Carron, David F. (Box 22)
      - Chickering, John Edw. "Johnny" (Box 22)
      - Cobb, Timothy Jon "Tim" (Box 22)
      - Contrada, Michael Gray "Mike" (includes Charles Vincent) (Box 22)
      - Cool, William Haver "Bill" (Box 22)
      - Coulter, Robert Frederick (Box 22)